(sighs)
(stammers)
(Sheldon:)You could have set Newton's
gravitational constant to one.
(Sheldon:)And, ugh, the whole thing reeks
of blueberry.
(Sheldon:)You know I can't stand
these scented markers.
(Leonard:)No one told you to taste them.
Come on, is-is this
good or not?
(sighs deeply)
(Sheldon:)It's good.
(Leonard:)Really?
I like it.
(Sheldon:)I think you're on to something.
(Leonard:)You do? You're not
messing with me?
(Sheldon:)Not at all.
(Sheldon:)In fact,
I have got something
(Sheldon:)for just such
an occasion.
(Sheldon:)I was starting to think
(Sheldon:)I might never get a chance
to give it to you.
(Sheldon:)Good job.
(Leonard:)You're giving me a sticker?
(Sheldon:)Not just a sticker.
(Sheldon:)That is a sticker of a kitty
saying, "Me-wow!"
(Leonard:)I'm not a preschooler.
(stammers)
Fine, I'll take it back.
I earned this!
Back off!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪